armor now give me armor I need armor
your queen requires armor back me up
behind ya cheers see ya clear them out
laughs
ah
three two one
in three two one
flag captured too easy the flag is mine
capture their little flag take the enemy
flag
ah don't let them take my flag protect
my flag Defender bloody flag
pick up the flag drop in the flag don't
let them capture our flag again they
captured our flag my flag get my flag
off the ground they dropped the flag
take it back
the scavs took our flag oy get my flag
back our flag Scythe flag returned
you're welcome
oh I have your flag try and stop me look
they gave me their flag get our flag
back
recover the damn flag they have a flag
take it back
let's go get him yes
all right
you and me yeah
oh
wow
my God
[Music]
ah
bloody hell damn it
take them out
oh are you done
quit hiding behind your Shield big girl
softy
hang with rat bags die like rat bags
oh champ you've gone soft you look
better than your fight
shine
I warned you boys
should have listened
Summer Shack Avenged
down you go big man
and stay down
give up
you're embarrassing yourself always
wanted one of you in my collection
as the queen decrees
kneel before your queen come on fight
back
oh your blood's all gone
no time for dramatic showdowns we're
scrapping here
I'm not gonna let a vlog in a spooky
mask take me down
it's like bashing watermelons on a rope
oh nice left big girl
I don't get clever with your queen
block a bug on a windscreen ah put your
little sword away
did you think you had an edge how
embarrassing
above you above us
behind you they're behind us down there
they're below us
they're in front of us they're just
ahead on the left on your left on your
right on the right someone's sneaking
around
we're not alone in here take him there
they are they brought one back ah they
revived the rap bag think you can take
me let's find out
come on then
gutless sniper ahead get the sniper hey
fall back or die
fall back
come on let's go go I move get ready
here it comes
follow me I'm going in
who wants to see some Carnage follow me
group up on me team to me Heal Me patch
me up foreign
good stuff much better
[Music]
oh I wanted a scar I owe you one
thanks
hey what g'day hi I am the junker Queen
I am the queen
the junker Queen stands with you my
Throne is where I say it is
attacking
what's this
defend this spot
hold this position
yeah ready
I'm with ya lead the way you lead the
way
for now here they come incoming
are any of you even trying
you're making this too easy you lot just
lost
how many of you drongos are there thanks
for bunching up
you know you're allowed to fart back
yeah oh I've taken naps harder than you
weak you're all awake hello I'm just
getting started
you're allowed to hit back one by one by
one come on come on
pathetic
lie down
my entire realm in plain view
this is the one that counts last chance
to kick their teeth in you want to lose
this to them I don't like losing you
won't like it either they don't stand a
chance
I think I'm getting another trophy for
me throne room today your honorary
wastelanders
let's go smash some heads everybody
holds nobody runs
get it done or else
finally some action
get out of my way
come on mate try to keep up
oh should have docked ha ax wins you
lose
you call that a fight oh down goes
another one
down goes another Pretender
plenty of Carnage what a wonderful day
you don't play with Carnage
did that hurt
good
sharp enough for you how's that edge
treating you oh might here it comes
you're in for it now
who wants their guts handed to him
none of you can stop me
we're doing this without a Healer then
you softies need a Healer give me
Shields
I need Shields oi why don't I have
shields yet
Shield me nah nah I want that objective
take the objective to the objective
fight here and fight hard
claiming the objective get over here
stop lagging about and get over here
defend the objective hold the objective
stay on the objective poor old Tanya
hide
where do you think you're going
stay on the objective
they're in our territory drive them back
they're taking our Point get him don't
let them take what's ours I push that
payload back
they're moving the payload get on them
knock them off the payload just a little
longer hold them back
push them back or answer to me
I'm on the payload get over here
my payload's moving pylon
I have the payload everyone relax
how come this payload doesn't move
faster when you kick it do I need to
chain you to the payload get back here
don't let them take my payload
stay on the payload block the payload
get on the payload and slow it down stop
the payload oi get on the payload or
I'll nail you to it
hey hey stick to the payload why is my
payload stopped move in and cut him down
we're running out of time attack
time's up get in there all hail the
queen
no one can stop me
calm down I'm coming on my way
oh
ah
let's take the fight to him
forward push forward now nearly head
yeah didn't they
save you thank me later you owe me one
yeah ah don't know why I saved you you
only lose if you stay down lucky shot my
turn
finally a decent scrap that I've got
plenty of teeth left
there'll be consequences for that
beat me Lord hell you will that's no way
to treat your queen
that is it
looks like somebody wants the death
penalty I'm getting back in there a
challenger I like those
yeah nobody reigns forever I'm up who
needs cutting
your coin thanks ya she's gone into
hiding again don't let her sneak up on
you find her before she finds us
oh looks like we found you after all
can't hide now cause you're dead
assassin down
assassin stomping time you ready
you hear that assassin
's gulking Twix I hear an assassin call
this a fair fight get off ow
bloody oh how you reckon she's hanging
on that wall
bet you I can hit that assassin with my
knife there she is knock her off the
wall assassin's still working about drag
that assassin down and take her out get
that assassin she's after ya stab her
before she stabs you
here she comes
finally
enforcer down
enforcer's done keep moving
this one thinks he's tougher and fossa
nice armor on that one let's cut it off
that enforces still breathing out air
why is that enforcer still standing
big man's missing some bits but he's
still fighting
big man's getting sloppy don't leave the
big one standing take out the Big Man
heavy assault's still up take him down
is anyone gonna get that sniper gonna
break that sniper rifle over my knee
sniper there there she is there's the
sniper these tiny devils are a waste of
my time
grunts ripped them to pieces
let's give these grunts a kicking
you should have finished the job mate I
always come back
[Music]
oh
set up here we need defenses here they
got a shield generator bloody cheats
their Shield generators in pieces
Shield generator there sorry about that
I guess
oh whoops
oh
take cover
save some for the rest of us nice one
that's the way not sure even I could
have done better good one Mako
show them what's what champ
would you look at that red jump Gotta
Kill
that's it for them anyone want to arm
wrestle all dead
you call that a fight oh no killing my
mates
ah get up here over here find their
teleporter they've got a teleporter find
it teleporters down and dusted
there's the teleporter thanks
turret destroyed
turret crushed they built a turret enemy
turret scrap it turret up ahead almost
time for a rampage my ultimate's almost
ready
can't Rampage yet my ultimate is
charging no Rampage yet let's give him a
Fighting Chance
get ready I'm about to go on a rampage
Rampage time watch him scatter time for
the Reckoning
let's take him to the Wasteland
I'm ready to Rampage time to go on a
rampage all right fine
sure oh watch here I'm watching this
position got my eyes on this spot
ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha
move the robot now push the robot robot
needs shoving they're pushing my robot
stop the robot we're outnumbered
outnumbered they've finally got a fair
fight
over here over there watch over here
keep your eyes here look here
not unless you want that table broken
over your head the knife's called Gracie
the ax is Carnage and me
I'm your queen
are you lot ready for some Bloodshed is
this one a scrap or a heist I wasn't
listening
think you can keep up
before we go out there I gotta warn you
I'm gonna yell at you a lot not because
I don't like you well because I care or
any of that it's just because I'm really
good at this
shut here's the plan do what I do listen
to what I say and don't screw this up
sure sure I'm watching you
have you got a hamster in that Mech
didn't I say I'd rip out your tongue if
I saw you again
right after the mission mark my words
yeah the ears are next
you look like a Bruiser want to be my
bodyguard
well I'm pretty sure I'm ahead I could
have run OverWatch much better than you
I would have caught all the bad guys
then cut their heads off how many widows
have you made roughly
I've met mossies with more brains than
you folks we've got an education system
ah both brothers on the same team better
make up before I smash your heads
together let's see we've got a bot an
Angel and the stupidest man alive does
that put us ahead or behind
I don't see what's so fancy about Rome
hardly any scrap heaps at all all right
ladies let's teach these boys a lesson
Portugal why on Earth are we in Portugal
behave yourself folks I can still have
you executed is there a kind of dingo
that is also a shark
some Ninja wish one of those big
underwater robots would attack I don't
need a Mech to fight then got any room
in that Mech champ I want to take some
souvenirs doctor have I really got to
eat vegetables it's like crunch crunch
crunch how long have I got to chew these
have I seen you before
you're the one who kicked redneck in the
Wicker Basket I thought a bunch of you
bastions once you all had wheels and big
sharp teeth ain't easy is it being in
charge of killers and Mad Men we got a
lot in common
shame I'm gonna kill you someday
yeah well I'm what's the word starts
with e
that's the one and don't you forget it
are you on average more mechanical or
more human
trying to figure out whether to scrap
you for parts
Mako the Wreckers want you back thought
you might like to know
they'll hate that I'll pass it along
what's the biggest Dax you could make
out of hard light maybe you wouldn't
jump I need you to make me something
else
a robot guard dog for me dirt Garden
maybe it can fly you decide a suit of
armor right but one that shouts my name
I need a slot bucket that's bulletproof
and don't you dare ask why a grenade
launcher with one trigger three barrels
paint glitter and nails
on second thought that might have been a
dream I had there's one stomp him got
something to kill here enemy here where
the hell is the rest of my team
this is my team asleep or what where is
everyone I need someone to shout it
hmm
oh I do love Neon
yeah
we have the robot get over here but get
pushing or I'll take your legs off
ha robot's mine they took the robot get
it back took my robot did they bad move
I want that robot back let's go
look at that push what go
stick with the robot we're moving
they're moving the barricade stop him
stop them pushing and do it now they're
pushing ahead
keep pushing or get shoved we're moving
it don't let up don't stop pushing now
they have the lead take it back we need
to catch up you lot of making me fall
behind we're catching up
yes we're gonna take the lead
we can take the lead if you don't screw
up
don't let them take the lead they take a
lead I'm taking heads they're catching
up don't leave the robot and we win
stay with the robot and we got this
don't Scamper off now stay with the
robot we got one shot at stopping him
and this is it take him down and it's
over
stop him and we win
[Music]
Gracie come here Gracie come on back
Gracie I need you Gracie to me Gracie my
hand needs a knife in it
where's my knife
knife I need a knife
knife got a little knife in you
give me back my knife
Gracie bring him over hey got something
and you got there
your queen summons you
yank haha
come here let's chat
strike the grit out of your knickers and
move toy pick up your feet you drongos
whoa let's go win this thing
stop mucking around and move
no time for whinging move out
oh
[Music]
reckoning's done I win again
ha ha loot them and let's go
no Champions here
nothing left but scrap
should have got out the way
oh someone Shot Ya
hot enough it's only Buckshot you got
too close didn't ya you're scattered
mate put a dent in your armor there
and You're Dead next can't fly Kenya and
down you go
nobody beats gravity mate I feel like
hot trash
something's wrong
ah don't feel right break that line
good on you
hot enough for you I was born to rule
it ain't a party until someone's dead
one of you numpties owes me a pint
anybody want a face full of ax
bow down your queen says charge knife to
see ya
let's go let's go
you know it I know it
I'm just that good
that's right
Bow Down
call me junker goddess
damn right I'm the Champion
I am your queen
sure yeah don't mention it no worries
you look like a Bruiser want to be my
bodyguard
huh I think you can take care of
yourself
no sorry I'd rip out your tongue if I
saw you again
clean
until waterfall upon my ears
right after the mission mark my words
yeah the ears are next
Genji remember the time you tripped over
your sword in training
some Ninja
it only happened once once was enough
how many widows have you made roughly I
do not keep track
well I'm pretty sure I'm ahead
so I'm trying to ask everybody this what
is your favorite animal is there a kind
of dingo that is also a shark uh yeah I
can see it I've met mothis with more
brains than you folks with all the
respect my lady I believe that's a knock
against the junkertown education system
we've got an education system I could
have run OverWatch much better than you
and what would you have done differently
I would have caught all the bad guys
then cut their heads off
hmm
tempting
on average more mechanical or more human
why
trying to figure out whether to scrap
you for parts
hmm
consider the railgun before you decide
maiko the Wreckers want you back thought
you might like to know
um
like that oh pass it along what's the
biggest decks you could make out of hard
light a kilometer tall
but you would not be able to wield it
maybe you wouldn't have I seen you
before
it's possible life passed through drunk
it down once or twice
I know kicked redneck in the wicker
basket
he started it I thought a bunch of you
bastians once you all had wheels and big
sharp teeth
on second thought that might have been a
dream I had
I'm easy is it being in charge of
killers and Mad Men no
but I welcome the challenge we got a lot
in common
shame I'm gonna kill you someday
[Music]
I need you to make me something else
a robot guard dog for me dirt Garden
maybe it can fly you decide a suit of
armor right but one that shouts my name
I need a slot bucket that's bulletproof
and don't you dare ask why a grenade
launcher with one trigger three barrels
paint glitter and nails
fine but give me a challenge next
I'm easy is it being in charge of
killers and Mad Men no
but I welcome the challenge there's
nothing about you in my files no images
no documents nothing yeah well on what's
the word starts with e
enigmatic that's the one and don't you
forget it have you got a hamster in that
Mech
um no sure sure I'm watching you anyone
want to hear my favorite joke about the
periodic table not unless you want that
table broken over your head
[Music]